[
  {
    "category": "Know Your History",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "points": 100,
        "question": "When was the first AWS re:Invent?",
        "answer": "2012",
        "answerType": "NUMBER"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "points": 200,
        "question": "What Amazon-favorite sport was introduced in re:Invent attendees in 2016?",
        "answer": "Broomball",
        "answerType": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "points": 300,
        "question": "What world record was set at the 2017 re:Invent Tatonka Challenge?",
        "answer": "Largest chicken wing eating contest: 214 people",
        "answerType": "STRING",
        "alternativeAnswers": [
          "wing eating contest",
          "largest wing eating contest",
          "biggest wing eating contest",
          "largest chicken wing eating contest",
          "biggest chicken wing eating contest"
        ]
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "points": 400,
        "question": "Which year were both the ECS (Elastic Container Service) and Lambda announced at re:Invent?",
        "answer": "2014",
        "answerType": "NUMBER"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "The Main Event",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": 5,
        "points": 100,
        "question": "What webinar helps people learn about re:Invent leading up to the big event?",
        "answer": "How to re:Invent",
        "answerType": "STRING",
        "alternativeAnswers": [
          "how to reinvent"
        ]
      },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "points": 200,
        "question": "How many casinos does the re:Invent campus span this year (2018)?",
        "answer": "7",
        "answerType": "NUMBER"
      },
      {
        "id": 7,
        "points": 300,
        "question": "What year did twitch.tv/aws start streaming at re:Invent?",
        "answer": "2016",
        "answerType": "NUMBER"
      },
      {
        "id": 8,
        "points": 400,
        "question": "How many chalk talks are scheduled for re:Invent 2018?",
        "answer": "592",
        "answerType": "NUMBER"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Let's Get Musical",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": 9,
        "points": 100,
        "question": "What genre of music is historically chosen for the re:play party?",
        "answer": "EDM",
        "answerType": "STRING",
        "alternativeAnswers": [
          "electronica",
          "DJ",
          "electronic dance music",
          "electronic music",
          "house music",
          "house"
        ]
      },
      {
        "id": 10,
        "points": 200,
        "question": "Who usually announces the DJ for re:play?",
        "answer": "Werner Vogels",
        "answerType": "STRING",
        "alternativeAnswers": []
      },
      {
        "id": 11,
        "points": 300,
        "question": "What venue hosts the re:play party?",
        "answer": "The Linq",
        "answerType": "STRING",
        "alternativeAnswers": [
          "the link",
          "linq",
          "link"
        ]
      },
      {
        "id": 12,
        "points": 400,
        "question": "Who was the re:play DJ at the 2013 re:Invent?",
        "answer": "DeadMau5",
        "answerType": "STRING",
        "alternativeAnswers": [
          "deadmau5",
          "Joel Thomas Zimmerman",
          "Joel Zimmerman",
          "dead mouse"
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "People, Places, and Things",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": 13,
        "points": 100,
        "question": "What sports star made a surprise experience at Midnight Madness in 2017?",
        "answer": "Shaq",
        "answerType": "STRING",
        "alternativeAnswers": [
          "Shaquille O'Neal",
          "DJ Shaquille O'Neal",
          "DJ Diesel",
          "Diesel",
          "DJ Shaq"
        ]
      },
      {
        "id": 14,
        "points": 200,
        "question": "Which AWS Engineer both appeared in the 2018 keynote, and also wrote this demo?",
        "answer": "Clare Liguori (hi!)",
        "answerType": "STRING",
        "alternativeAnswers": [
          "Clare Liguori",
          "Clare",
          "clareliguori",
          "@clare_liguori"
        ]
      },
      {
        "id": 15,
        "points": 300,
        "question": "What restaurant is located in both the Venetian and the Palazzo?",
        "answer": "Grand Lux Cafe",
        "answerType": "STRING",
        "alternativeAnswers": [
        ]
      },
      {
        "id": 16,
        "points": 400,
        "question": "What AWS speaker keynoted \"Tuesday Night Live\" in 2016?",
        "answer": "James Hamilton",
        "answerType": "STRING",
        "alternativeAnswers": [
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
]
